Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2016
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Ensemble Uusinta (Jozsef Hars, conductor, Marko Portin, clarinet, Väinö Jalkanen, piano, Max Savikangas, viola, Pinja Laine, violoncello, Malla Vivolin, flute, and Maria Puusaari, violin) and student composers Igor Coelho A.S. Marques, Colin Tucker, Ryan Suleiman, Peter Kramer, and Young Woo Yoo acknowledge applause after a concert of student compositions at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_11, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name student composers with Ensemble Uusinta.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_283.tif)
- Student composer Igor Coelho A.S. Marques poses for a portrait with Malla Vivolin, flute and Maria Puusaari, violin of Ensemble Uusinta after a performance of student compositions at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_11, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name student composer Igor Coelho A.S.Marques with memmbers of Ensemble Uusinta Malla Vivolin, flute (lrft) Maria Puusaari (~1.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_284.tif)
- Arditti Quartet (Irvine Arditti, violin, Ashot Sarkissjan, violin, Lucas Fels, violoncello, and Ralph Ehlers, viola) before a performance at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_11, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Arditti Quartet.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_285.tif)
- Arditti Quartet (Irvine Arditti, violin, Ashot Sarkissjan, violin, Lucas Fels, violoncello, and Ralph Ehlers, viola) during a performance at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_11, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name ARDITTI QUARTET JIB.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_286.tif)
- Arditti Quartet (Irvine Arditti, violin, Ashot Sarkissjan, violin, Lucas Fels, violoncello, and Ralph Ehlers, viola) during a performance at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_11, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name JIB ARDITTI QUARTET.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_287.tif)
- Arditti Quartet (Irvine Arditti, violin, Ashot Sarkissjan, violin, Lucas Fels, violoncello, and Ralph Ehlers, viola) during a performance of Joshua Fineberg's La Quintana for string quartet and electronics at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_11, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Arditti Quartet composer Joshua Fineberg.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_288.tif)
- Composer Joshua Fineberg acknowledges the Arditti Quartet (Irvine Arditti, violin, Ashot Sarkissjan, violin, Lucas Fels, violoncello, and Ralph Ehlers, viola) after a performance of Fineberg's La Quintana for string quartet and electronics at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_11, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Joshua Fineberg and Arditti Quartet.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_289.tif)
- Composer Hans Abrahamsen acknowledges the Arditti Quartet (Irvine Arditti, violin, Ashot Sarkissjan, violin, Lucas Fels, violoncello, and Ralph Ehlers, viola) after a performance of Abrahamsen's String Quartet No. 4 at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_11, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name composer Hans Abrahamsen.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_290.tif)
- Composer Hans Abrahamsen acknowledges the Arditti Quartet (Irvine Arditti, violin, Ashot Sarkissjan, violin, Lucas Fels, violoncello, and Ralph Ehlers, viola) after a performance of Abrahamsen's String Quartet No. 4 at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_11, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Arditti Quartet with composer Hans Abrahamsen.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_291.tif)
- Composer David Felder acknowledges the Arditti Quartet (Irvine Arditti, violin, Ashot Sarkissjan, violin, Lucas Fels, violoncello, and Ralph Ehlers, viola) after a performance of Felder's Netivot at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_11, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name composer David Felder.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_292.tif)
- Composer David Felder acknowledges the Arditti Quartet (Irvine Arditti, violin, Ashot Sarkissjan, violin, Lucas Fels, violoncello, and Ralph Ehlers, viola) after a performance of Felder's Netivot at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_11, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Arditti Quartet and composer David Felder.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_293.tif)
- Composer David Felder acknowledges the Arditti Quartet (Irvine Arditti, violin, Ashot Sarkissjan, violin, Lucas Fels, violoncello, and Ralph Ehlers, viola) after a performance of Felder's Netivot at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_11, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name composer David Felder and Arditti Quartet JIB.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_294.tif)
- Composer David Felder acknowledges the Arditti Quartet (Irvine Arditti, violin, Ashot Sarkissjan, violin, Lucas Fels, violoncello, and Ralph Ehlers, viola) after a performance of Felder's Netivot at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_11, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name JIB composer David Felder and Arditti Quartet.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_295.tif)
- Composer David Felder acknowledges the Arditti Quartet (Irvine Arditti, violin, Ashot Sarkissjan, violin, Lucas Fels, violoncello, and Ralph Ehlers, viola) after a performance of Felder's Netivot at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_11, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Lippes Concert Hall Saturday.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_296.tif)
- Composer David Felder acknowledges the Arditti Quartet (Irvine Arditti, violin, Ashot Sarkissjan, violin, Lucas Fels, violoncello, and Ralph Ehlers, viola) after a performance of Felder's Netivot at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_11, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name JIB 2016.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_297.tif)
- Conductor JoAnn Falletta and the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra rehearse at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_12, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4621.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_298.tif)
- Conductor JoAnn Falletta and the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra rehearse at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_12, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name rehearsal Buffalo Philharmonic.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_299.tif)
- Conductor JoAnn Falletta and the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra rehearse at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_12, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4623.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_300.tif)
- Conductor JoAnn Falletta with the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra during rehearsal as composer David Felder looks on at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_12, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name BPO rehearsal composer David Felder.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_301.tif)
- Conductor JoAnn Falletta with the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra during rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_12, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4625.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_302.tif)
- Composer Chinary Ung talks with conductor JoAnn Falletta and the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra during rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_12, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name BPO JIB 2016COMPOSER cHINARY ung.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_303.tif)
- Composer Chinary Ung talks with conductor JoAnn Falletta and the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra during rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_12, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4630 composer Chinary UNG BPO.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_304.tif)
- Composer Chinary Ung talks with conductor JoAnn Falletta and the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra during rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_12, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name BPO and composer Chinary Ung JIB.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_305.tif)
- Composer Chinary Ung talks with conductor JoAnn Falletta and the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra during rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_12, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name composer Chinary Ung and BPO.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_306.tif)
- Composer Hans Abrahamsen greets conductor JoAnn Falletta and the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra during rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_12, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name composer Hans Abrahamsen with BPO JIB 2016.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_307.tif)
- Composer Hans Abrahamsen talks with conductor JoAnn Falletta and the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra during rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_12, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4634composer Hans Abrahamsen and BPO.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_308.tif)
- Composer Hans Abrahamsen talks with conductor JoAnn Falletta and the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra during rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_12, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name BPO and composer Hans Abrahamsen.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_309.tif)
- Composer Hans Abrahamsen with conductor JoAnn Falletta and the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra during rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_12, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4636 Hans Abrahmsen AND bpo.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_310.tif)
- Composer Hans Abrahamsen with conductor JoAnn Falletta and the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra during rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_12, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name composer Hans Abrahamsen and BPO.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_311.tif)
- Conductor Michael Lewanski, Susan Ung, viola, and Ensemble Dal Niente (Greg Beyer and Stephen Solook, percussion, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, and Mabel Kwan, piano) rehearse Chinary Ung's Singing inside aura at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Untitled-1 (2).tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_312.tif)
- Composer David Felder speaking to student composers at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name David Felder greeting composers and student composers.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_313.tif)
- Conductor Jozsef Hars and Ensemble Uusinta (Malla Vivolin, flute, Maria Puusaari, violin, Marko Portin, clarinet, Pinja Laine, violoncello, John Smigielski, Jonathan Hepfer, and Alexander Chimienti, percussion) in a performance of Chinary Ung's Oracle at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Untitled-1.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_314.tif)
Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog.
Subjects
June in Buffalo (Festival) (Buffalo, N.Y.)--Photographs; Composers--Photographs; Music festivals--New York (State)--Buffalo--Photographs; Musicians--Photographs
Genres
Digital photographs; Portrait photographs
Associated Material
Related Resources
Related Resources in the Music Library
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2000
Mus. Arc. 18
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2000 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2001
Mus. Arc. 19
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2001 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2002
Mus. Arc. 20
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2002 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2003
Mus. Arc. 21
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2003 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2004
Mus. Arc. 25
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2004 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2005
Mus. Arc. 27
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2005 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2006
Mus. Arc. 29
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2006 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2007
Mus. Arc. 38
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2007 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2008
Mus. Arc. 39
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2008 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2009
Mus. Arc. 50
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2009 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2010
Mus. Arc. 55
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2010 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2011
Mus. Arc. 56
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2011 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2012
Mus. Arc. 60
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2012 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2013
Mus. Arc. 66
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2013 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2014
Mus. Arc. 67
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2014 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2015
Mus. Arc. 74
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2015 June in Buffalo.
June in Buffalo Photograph Collection
A selection of images from the June in Buffalo festivals are available through University at Buffalo Libraries Digital Collections.